<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-01-07T05:23:12+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Celebrating My First GitHub Website A Journey Of Learning And Success.</title><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2024/post-bibliography/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Celebrating My First GitHub Website A Journey Of Learning And Success."/><published>2024-01-06T15:20:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-06T15:20:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2024/post-bibliography</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2024/post-bibliography/"><![CDATA[<ol> <li> <p>Introduction: Embarking on a journey of learning and success! Welcome to my first blog post on my website! This website is not only a place for me to explore new projects, but also a platform for me to showcase my skills through write-ups and blogs. I am excited to embark on this journey of learning and success, particularly in the world of ethical hacking and programming. Join me as I share my experiences, insights, and achievements along the way. I can’t wait to see where this journey takes me!</p> </li> <li> <p>Setting the foundation: Why GitHub is a game-changer! Setting the foundation: Why GitHub is a game-changer!</p> </li> </ol> <p>When it comes to programming and web development, GitHub has become an essential tool for all aspiring developers. As I dive deeper into my journey of learning and success, I can’t help but emphasize just how instrumental GitHub has been in helping me showcase my skills and collaborate with other like-minded individuals.</p> <p>One of the key reasons why GitHub is a game-changer is its ability to make version control seamless. Gone are the days of juggling multiple files and folders, trying to keep track of changes made by different team members. With GitHub, I can easily manage and track all revisions, contributing to a streamlined development process.</p> <p>Moreover, GitHub’s collaborative nature has opened up a world of opportunities for me to connect with fellow programmers. Through pull requests and discussions on code, I have been able to learn from others, receive feedback on my own projects, and contribute to open-source initiatives. It truly is a platform that fosters growth and community.</p> <p>Stay tuned for the next section of my journey, where I will share some of the exciting projects I have been working on and how GitHub has played a pivotal role in their development. Until then, keep exploring, learning, and embracing the power of GitHub!</p> <ol> <li>Unleashing my creativity: The unique elements of my GitHub website Unleashing my creativity: The unique elements of my GitHub website</li> </ol> <p>Creating my first GitHub website has allowed me to explore and express my creativity in ways I never imagined. With the flexibility and customization options that GitHub provides, I have been able to design a website that truly reflects my personal style and showcases my skills.</p> <p>One of the unique elements of my GitHub website is the interactive portfolio section. Instead of just listing my projects, I have made it a point to include visually appealing screenshots, brief descriptions, and even links to live demos. This not only engages visitors but also gives them a glimpse into the quality of my work.</p> <p>Another standout feature of my website is the blog section. Here, I regularly share my insights, experiences, and learnings from my coding journey. It not only helps me solidify my understanding of concepts but also allows me to connect with a wider audience and contribute to the programming community.</p> <p>But perhaps the most exciting element of my GitHub website is the integration of a personal touch. I have included a dedicated “About Me” page where I share my passions, hobbies, and aspirations. This humanizes my website and gives visitors a chance to get to know the person behind the code.</p> <p>In the next section, I will delve deeper into the technical aspects of building my GitHub website, from choosing the right templates to mastering the art of responsive design. Get ready to be inspired as I share my journey of creating a website that is not only functional but also visually captivating and user-friendly.</p> <ol> <li>A celebration of connections: Finding support and camaraderie within the GitHub community Building my first GitHub website has not only been a journey of learning and success, but it has also been an opportunity to connect with a vibrant and supportive community. Through the GitHub platform, I have discovered a network of like-minded individuals who share the same passion for coding and web development.</li> </ol> <p>The sense of camaraderie within the GitHub community is truly remarkable. Whether it’s seeking advice on a coding challenge or receiving feedback on my website design, I have always found someone willing to lend a helping hand. The community is filled with talented developers who are not only willing to share their knowledge but also celebrate each other’s achievements.</p> <p>Finding support within the GitHub community has been instrumental in my growth as a coder. In addition to the technical insights I have gained, I have also been inspired by the success stories and personal journeys of fellow developers. It is truly a celebration of connections, where we lift each other up and push each other to reach new heights.</p> <p>I encourage anyone starting their GitHub journey to actively engage with the community. Participate in discussions, attend virtual meetups, and contribute to open-source projects. The connections you make and the support you receive will undoubtedly enhance your learning experience and open doors to new opportunities.</p> <p>In the next section, I will share some tips and tricks I have learned along the way to optimize my GitHub website for search engines and increase its visibility. Stay tuned as I unveil the secrets to driving traffic and attracting a wider audience to my online portfolio. Get ready to take your GitHub website to the next level!</p> <ol> <li>Spreading the joy: Showcasing my GitHub website and giving it the spotlight it deserves Building my first GitHub website has been an exhilarating experience, and now it’s time to spread the joy and give my creation the spotlight it deserves! There’s nothing quite like the feeling of sharing your hard work with the world and seeing it be appreciated.</li> </ol> <p>To showcase my GitHub website, I will start by sharing it on social media platforms. Platforms like Twitter, LinkedIn, and Instagram are perfect for reaching a wider audience and getting valuable feedback. I’ll create engaging posts that highlight the unique features and design elements of my website, leaving people excited to visit and explore.</p> <p>Additionally, I will connect with other bloggers and influencers in the coding and web development community. Collaborating with others on guest blog posts or featuring my website in their content can significantly increase its visibility and attract new visitors. Not only will this help spread the word about my website, but it will also create opportunities for networking and collaboration.</p> <p>Lastly, I will optimize my GitHub website for search engines. By incorporating relevant keywords in my page titles, meta descriptions, and content, I can improve my website’s ranking in search results. This will make it easier for people searching for coding resources or web development projects to discover my website.</p> <p>Spreading the joy and giving my GitHub website the attention it deserves is an important step in my journey of learning and success. It’s time to share my passion with the world and inspire others to embark on their own coding adventures. Stay tuned as I unveil more strategies to elevate my GitHub website and make it shine!</p> <ol> <li>From learner to teacher: Empowering others through sharing my GitHub success story From learner to teacher: Empowering others through sharing my GitHub success story</li> </ol> <p>One of the most fulfilling aspects of my journey in building my first GitHub website is the opportunity to inspire and empower others. I strongly believe that knowledge is meant to be shared, and in doing so, we can create a supportive and thriving community of learners.</p> <p>Through my blog and social media platforms, I will not only showcase my GitHub website but also share the lessons I’ve learned along the way. I will write in-depth tutorials, step-by-step guides, and troubleshooting tips to help aspiring coders and web developers navigate the world of GitHub and website creation.</p> <p>By sharing the challenges I faced and how I overcame them, I hope to motivate others who may feel overwhelmed or discouraged. I want to let them know that everyone starts somewhere, and with dedication and persistence, they can achieve their goals.</p> <p>In addition, I will encourage interaction and engagement with my audience. Through comments sections and live Q&amp;A sessions, I will create a space for open dialogue and collaboration. This will further foster a sense of community and provide a support system for learners at various stages of their coding journey.</p> <p>Through sharing my GitHub success story, I aim to empower others and create a positive ripple effect of inspiration and growth. Together, we can celebrate each other’s achievements and create a vibrant network of passionate learners. Stay tuned as I embark on this exciting phase of my journey, and join me in spreading the joy of coding and success!</p> <ol> <li>A heartfelt thank you: Wrapping up my journey with gratitude and anticipation for what’s to come Throughout this journey of learning and success, I have been overwhelmed with gratitude for the support and encouragement I’ve received from friends, family, and the coding community. I am truly blessed to have such an incredible network of people who have believed in me and cheered me on every step of the way.</li> </ol> <p>I want to take a moment to express my heartfelt gratitude to each and every one of you. Your words of encouragement, kind comments, and shared experiences have meant the world to me. Without your unwavering support, I would not have had the courage to embark on this journey, let alone achieve the milestones I’ve reached.</p> <p>I also want to thank the countless online resources, tutorials, and forums that have played a pivotal role in my learning process. The generosity of the coding community in sharing knowledge and providing guidance is truly awe-inspiring. I am forever grateful for the wealth of information that is freely accessible to aspiring coders like myself.</p> <p>As I wrap up this chapter of my journey, I can’t help but feel excited for what the future holds. Building my first GitHub website was just the beginning, and I am eager to continue expanding my skills, exploring new technologies, and sharing my knowledge with even more people.</p> <p>I look forward to the challenges and triumphs that lie ahead, and I invite you all to join me on this joyous ride. Together, we can continue to learn, grow, and celebrate the incredible world of coding. Thank you all once again, and stay tuned for more exciting updates on my coding adventures!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="bib"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[My FirtWebsite]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with table of contents</title><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2023/table-of-contents/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with table of contents"/><published>2023-03-20T15:59:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-03-20T15:59:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2023/table-of-contents</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2023/table-of-contents/"><![CDATA[<p>This post shows how to add a table of contents in the beginning of the post.</p> <h2 id="adding-a-table-of-contents">Adding a Table of Contents</h2> <p>To add a table of contents to a post, simply add</p> <div class="language-yml highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="na">toc</span><span class="pi">:</span>
  <span class="na">beginning</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="kc">true</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>to the front matter of the post. The table of contents will be automatically generated from the headings in the post.</p> <h3 id="example-of-sub-heading-1">Example of Sub-Heading 1</h3> <p>Jean shorts raw denim Vice normcore, art party High Life PBR skateboard stumptown vinyl kitsch. Four loko meh 8-bit, tousled banh mi tilde forage Schlitz dreamcatcher twee 3 wolf moon. Chambray asymmetrical paleo salvia, sartorial umami four loko master cleanse drinking vinegar brunch. <a href="https://www.pinterest.com">Pinterest</a> DIY authentic Schlitz, hoodie Intelligentsia butcher trust fund brunch shabby chic Kickstarter forage flexitarian. Direct trade <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cold-pressed_juice">cold-pressed</a> meggings stumptown plaid, pop-up taxidermy. Hoodie XOXO fingerstache scenester Echo Park. Plaid ugh Wes Anderson, freegan pug selvage fanny pack leggings pickled food truck DIY irony Banksy.</p> <h3 id="example-of-another-sub-heading-1">Example of another Sub-Heading 1</h3> <p>Jean shorts raw denim Vice normcore, art party High Life PBR skateboard stumptown vinyl kitsch. Four loko meh 8-bit, tousled banh mi tilde forage Schlitz dreamcatcher twee 3 wolf moon. Chambray asymmetrical paleo salvia, sartorial umami four loko master cleanse drinking vinegar brunch. <a href="https://www.pinterest.com">Pinterest</a> DIY authentic Schlitz, hoodie Intelligentsia butcher trust fund brunch shabby chic Kickstarter forage flexitarian. Direct trade <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cold-pressed_juice">cold-pressed</a> meggings stumptown plaid, pop-up taxidermy. Hoodie XOXO fingerstache scenester Echo Park. Plaid ugh Wes Anderson, freegan pug selvage fanny pack leggings pickled food truck DIY irony Banksy.</p> <h2 id="table-of-contents-options">Table of Contents Options</h2> <p>If you want to learn more about how to customize the table of contents, you can check the <a href="https://github.com/toshimaru/jekyll-toc">jekyll-toc</a> repository.</p> <h3 id="example-of-sub-heading-2">Example of Sub-Heading 2</h3> <p>Jean shorts raw denim Vice normcore, art party High Life PBR skateboard stumptown vinyl kitsch. Four loko meh 8-bit, tousled banh mi tilde forage Schlitz dreamcatcher twee 3 wolf moon. Chambray asymmetrical paleo salvia, sartorial umami four loko master cleanse drinking vinegar brunch. <a href="https://www.pinterest.com">Pinterest</a> DIY authentic Schlitz, hoodie Intelligentsia butcher trust fund brunch shabby chic Kickstarter forage flexitarian. Direct trade <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cold-pressed_juice">cold-pressed</a> meggings stumptown plaid, pop-up taxidermy. Hoodie XOXO fingerstache scenester Echo Park. Plaid ugh Wes Anderson, freegan pug selvage fanny pack leggings pickled food truck DIY irony Banksy.</p> <h3 id="example-of-another-sub-heading-2">Example of another Sub-Heading 2</h3> <p>Jean shorts raw denim Vice normcore, art party High Life PBR skateboard stumptown vinyl kitsch. Four loko meh 8-bit, tousled banh mi tilde forage Schlitz dreamcatcher twee 3 wolf moon. Chambray asymmetrical paleo salvia, sartorial umami four loko master cleanse drinking vinegar brunch. <a href="https://www.pinterest.com">Pinterest</a> DIY authentic Schlitz, hoodie Intelligentsia butcher trust fund brunch shabby chic Kickstarter forage flexitarian. Direct trade <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cold-pressed_juice">cold-pressed</a> meggings stumptown plaid, pop-up taxidermy. Hoodie XOXO fingerstache scenester Echo Park. Plaid ugh Wes Anderson, freegan pug selvage fanny pack leggings pickled food truck DIY irony Banksy.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="toc"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a blog post with table of contents]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with giscus comments</title><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2022/giscus-comments/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with giscus comments"/><published>2022-12-10T15:59:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-10T15:59:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2022/giscus-comments</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2022/giscus-comments/"><![CDATA[<p>This post shows how to add GISCUS comments.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="external-services"/><category term="comments"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a blog post with giscus comments]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog</title><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog"/><published>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with redirect</title><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2022/redirect/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with redirect"/><published>2022-02-01T17:39:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-02-01T17:39:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2022/redirect</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2022/redirect/"><![CDATA[<p>Redirecting to another page.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[you can also redirect to assets like pdf]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with diagrams</title><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2021/diagrams/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with diagrams"/><published>2021-07-04T17:39:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-07-04T17:39:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2021/diagrams</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2021/diagrams/"><![CDATA[<p>This theme supports generating various diagrams from a text description using <a href="https://mermaid-js.github.io/mermaid/" target="\_blank">mermaid</a>. Previously, this was done using the <a href="https://github.com/zhustec/jekyll-diagrams" target="\_blank">jekyll-diagrams</a> plugin. For more information on this matter, see the <a href="https://github.com/alshedivat/al-folio/issues/1609#issuecomment-1656995674">related issue</a>. To disable the zooming feature, set <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">mermaid.zoomable</code> to <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">false</code> in this post frontmatter.</p> <h2 id="mermaid">Mermaid</h2> <p>The diagram below was generated by the following code:</p> <div class="language-markdown highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="p">```</span><span class="nl">mermaid
</span><span class="sb">sequenceDiagram
    participant John
    participant Alice
    Alice-&gt;&gt;John: Hello John, how are you?
    John--&gt;&gt;Alice: Great!</span>
<span class="p">```</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <pre><code class="language-mermaid">sequenceDiagram
    participant John
    participant Alice
    Alice-&gt;&gt;John: Hello John, how are you?
    John--&gt;&gt;Alice: Great!
</code></pre>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="formatting"/><category term="diagrams"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a blog post with diagrams]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a distill-style blog post</title><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2021/distill/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a distill-style blog post"/><published>2021-05-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-05-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2021/distill</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2021/distill/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="equations">Equations</h2> <p>This theme supports rendering beautiful math in inline and display modes using <a href="https://www.mathjax.org/">MathJax 3</a> engine. You just need to surround your math expression with <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">$$</code>, like <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">$$ E = mc^2 $$</code>. If you leave it inside a paragraph, it will produce an inline expression, just like \(E = mc^2\).</p> <p>To use display mode, again surround your expression with <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">$$</code> and place it as a separate paragraph. Here is an example:</p> \[\left( \sum_{k=1}^n a_k b_k \right)^2 \leq \left( \sum_{k=1}^n a_k^2 \right) \left( \sum_{k=1}^n b_k^2 \right)\] <p>Note that MathJax 3 is <a href="https://docs.mathjax.org/en/latest/upgrading/whats-new-3.0.html">a major re-write of MathJax</a> that brought a significant improvement to the loading and rendering speed, which is now <a href="http://www.intmath.com/cg5/katex-mathjax-comparison.php">on par with KaTeX</a>.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="citations">Citations</h2> <p>Citations are then used in the article body with the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">&lt;d-cite&gt;</code> tag. The key attribute is a reference to the id provided in the bibliography. The key attribute can take multiple ids, separated by commas.</p> <p>The citation is presented inline like this: <d-cite key="gregor2015draw"></d-cite> (a number that displays more information on hover). If you have an appendix, a bibliography is automatically created and populated in it.</p> <p>Distill chose a numerical inline citation style to improve readability of citation dense articles and because many of the benefits of longer citations are obviated by displaying more information on hover. However, we consider it good style to mention author last names if you discuss something at length and it fits into the flow well — the authors are human and it’s nice for them to have the community associate them with their work.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="footnotes">Footnotes</h2> <p>Just wrap the text you would like to show up in a footnote in a <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">&lt;d-footnote&gt;</code> tag. The number of the footnote will be automatically generated.<d-footnote>This will become a hoverable footnote.</d-footnote></p> <hr/> <h2 id="code-blocks">Code Blocks</h2> <p>Syntax highlighting is provided within <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">&lt;d-code&gt;</code> tags. An example of inline code snippets: <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">&lt;d-code language="html"&gt;let x = 10;&lt;/d-code&gt;</code>. For larger blocks of code, add a <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">block</code> attribute:</p> <d-code block="" language="javascript"> var x = 25; function(x) { return x * x; } </d-code> <p><strong>Note:</strong> <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">&lt;d-code&gt;</code> blocks do not look good in the dark mode. You can always use the default code-highlight using the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">highlight</code> liquid tag:</p> <figure class="highlight"><pre><code class="language-javascript" data-lang="javascript"><span class="kd">var</span> <span class="nx">x</span> <span class="o">=</span> <span class="mi">25</span><span class="p">;</span>
<span class="kd">function</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="nx">x</span><span class="p">)</span> <span class="p">{</span>
  <span class="k">return</span> <span class="nx">x</span> <span class="o">*</span> <span class="nx">x</span><span class="p">;</span>
<span class="p">}</span></code></pre></figure> <hr/> <h2 id="interactive-plots">Interactive Plots</h2> <p>You can add interative plots using plotly + iframes :framed_picture:</p> <div class="l-page"> <iframe src="/assets/plotly/demo.html" frameborder="0" scrolling="no" height="500px" width="100%" style="border: 1px dashed grey;"></iframe> </div> <p>The plot must be generated separately and saved into an HTML file. To generate the plot that you see above, you can use the following code snippet:</p> <figure class="highlight"><pre><code class="language-python" data-lang="python"><span class="kn">import</span> <span class="n">pandas</span> <span class="k">as</span> <span class="n">pd</span>
<span class="kn">import</span> <span class="n">plotly.express</span> <span class="k">as</span> <span class="n">px</span>
<span class="n">df</span> <span class="o">=</span> <span class="n">pd</span><span class="p">.</span><span class="nf">read_csv</span><span class="p">(</span>
  <span class="sh">'</span><span class="s">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/plotly/datasets/master/earthquakes-23k.csv</span><span class="sh">'</span>
<span class="p">)</span>
<span class="n">fig</span> <span class="o">=</span> <span class="n">px</span><span class="p">.</span><span class="nf">density_mapbox</span><span class="p">(</span>
  <span class="n">df</span><span class="p">,</span>
  <span class="n">lat</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="sh">'</span><span class="s">Latitude</span><span class="sh">'</span><span class="p">,</span>
  <span class="n">lon</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="sh">'</span><span class="s">Longitude</span><span class="sh">'</span><span class="p">,</span>
  <span class="n">z</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="sh">'</span><span class="s">Magnitude</span><span class="sh">'</span><span class="p">,</span>
  <span class="n">radius</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="mi">10</span><span class="p">,</span>
  <span class="n">center</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="nf">dict</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="n">lat</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="mi">0</span><span class="p">,</span> <span class="n">lon</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="mi">180</span><span class="p">),</span>
  <span class="n">zoom</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="mi">0</span><span class="p">,</span>
  <span class="n">mapbox_style</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="sh">"</span><span class="s">stamen-terrain</span><span class="sh">"</span><span class="p">,</span>
<span class="p">)</span>
<span class="n">fig</span><span class="p">.</span><span class="nf">show</span><span class="p">()</span>
<span class="n">fig</span><span class="p">.</span><span class="nf">write_html</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="sh">'</span><span class="s">assets/plotly/demo.html</span><span class="sh">'</span><span class="p">)</span></code></pre></figure> <hr/> <h2 id="details-boxes">Details boxes</h2> <p>Details boxes are collapsible boxes which hide additional information from the user. They can be added with the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">details</code> liquid tag:</p> <details><summary>Click here to know more</summary> <p>Additional details, where math \(2x - 1\) and <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">code</code> is rendered correctly.</p> </details> <hr/> <h2 id="layouts">Layouts</h2> <p>The main text column is referred to as the body. It is the assumed layout of any direct descendants of the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">d-article</code> element.</p> <div class="fake-img l-body"> <p>.l-body</p> </div> <p>For images you want to display a little larger, try <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">.l-page</code>:</p> <div class="fake-img l-page"> <p>.l-page</p> </div> <p>All of these have an outset variant if you want to poke out from the body text a little bit. For instance:</p> <div class="fake-img l-body-outset"> <p>.l-body-outset</p> </div> <div class="fake-img l-page-outset"> <p>.l-page-outset</p> </div> <p>Occasionally you’ll want to use the full browser width. For this, use <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">.l-screen</code>. You can also inset the element a little from the edge of the browser by using the inset variant.</p> <div class="fake-img l-screen"> <p>.l-screen</p> </div> <div class="fake-img l-screen-inset"> <p>.l-screen-inset</p> </div> <p>The final layout is for marginalia, asides, and footnotes. It does not interrupt the normal flow of <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">.l-body</code> sized text except on mobile screen sizes.</p> <div class="fake-img l-gutter"> <p>.l-gutter</p> </div> <hr/> <h2 id="other-typography">Other Typography?</h2> <p>Emphasis, aka italics, with <em>asterisks</em> (<code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">*asterisks*</code>) or <em>underscores</em> (<code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_underscores_</code>).</p> <p>Strong emphasis, aka bold, with <strong>asterisks</strong> or <strong>underscores</strong>.</p> <p>Combined emphasis with <strong>asterisks and <em>underscores</em></strong>.</p> <p>Strikethrough uses two tildes. <del>Scratch this.</del></p> <ol> <li>First ordered list item</li> <li>Another item ⋅⋅* Unordered sub-list.</li> <li>Actual numbers don’t matter, just that it’s a number ⋅⋅1. Ordered sub-list</li> <li>And another item.</li> </ol> <p>⋅⋅⋅You can have properly indented paragraphs within list items. Notice the blank line above, and the leading spaces (at least one, but we’ll use three here to also align the raw Markdown).</p> <p>⋅⋅⋅To have a line break without a paragraph, you will need to use two trailing spaces.⋅⋅ ⋅⋅⋅Note that this line is separate, but within the same paragraph.⋅⋅ ⋅⋅⋅(This is contrary to the typical GFM line break behaviour, where trailing spaces are not required.)</p> <ul> <li>Unordered list can use asterisks</li> <li>Or minuses</li> <li>Or pluses</li> </ul> <p><a href="https://www.google.com">I’m an inline-style link</a></p> <p><a href="https://www.google.com" title="Google's Homepage">I’m an inline-style link with title</a></p> <p><a href="https://www.mozilla.org">I’m a reference-style link</a></p> <p><a href="../blob/master/LICENSE">I’m a relative reference to a repository file</a></p> <p><a href="http://slashdot.org">You can use numbers for reference-style link definitions</a></p> <p>Or leave it empty and use the <a href="http://www.reddit.com">link text itself</a>.</p> <p>URLs and URLs in angle brackets will automatically get turned into links. http://www.example.com or <a href="http://www.example.com">http://www.example.com</a> and sometimes example.com (but not on Github, for example).</p> <p>Some text to show that the reference links can follow later.</p> <p>Here’s our logo (hover to see the title text):</p> <p>Inline-style: <img src="https://github.com/adam-p/markdown-here/raw/master/src/common/images/icon48.png" alt="alt text" title="Logo Title Text 1"/></p> <p>Reference-style: <img src="https://github.com/adam-p/markdown-here/raw/master/src/common/images/icon48.png" alt="alt text" title="Logo Title Text 2"/></p> <p>Inline <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">code</code> has <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">back-ticks around</code> it.</p> <div class="language-javascript highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="kd">var</span> <span class="nx">s</span> <span class="o">=</span> <span class="dl">"</span><span class="s2">JavaScript syntax highlighting</span><span class="dl">"</span><span class="p">;</span>
<span class="nf">alert</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="nx">s</span><span class="p">);</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <div class="language-python highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="n">s</span> <span class="o">=</span> <span class="sh">"</span><span class="s">Python syntax highlighting</span><span class="sh">"</span>
<span class="k">print</span> <span class="n">s</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>No language indicated, so no syntax highlighting.
But let's throw in a &lt;b&gt;tag&lt;/b&gt;.
</code></pre></div></div> <p>Colons can be used to align columns.</p> <table> <thead> <tr> <th>Tables</th> <th style="text-align: center">Are</th> <th style="text-align: right">Cool</th> </tr> </thead> <tbody> <tr> <td>col 3 is</td> <td style="text-align: center">right-aligned</td> <td style="text-align: right">$1600</td> </tr> <tr> <td>col 2 is</td> <td style="text-align: center">centered</td> <td style="text-align: right">$12</td> </tr> <tr> <td>zebra stripes</td> <td style="text-align: center">are neat</td> <td style="text-align: right">$1</td> </tr> </tbody> </table> <p>There must be at least 3 dashes separating each header cell. The outer pipes (|) are optional, and you don’t need to make the raw Markdown line up prettily. You can also use inline Markdown.</p> <table> <thead> <tr> <th>Markdown</th> <th>Less</th> <th>Pretty</th> </tr> </thead> <tbody> <tr> <td><em>Still</em></td> <td><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">renders</code></td> <td><strong>nicely</strong></td> </tr> <tr> <td>1</td> <td>2</td> <td>3</td> </tr> </tbody> </table> <blockquote> <p>Blockquotes are very handy in email to emulate reply text. This line is part of the same quote.</p> </blockquote> <p>Quote break.</p> <blockquote> <p>This is a very long line that will still be quoted properly when it wraps. Oh boy let’s keep writing to make sure this is long enough to actually wrap for everyone. Oh, you can <em>put</em> <strong>Markdown</strong> into a blockquote.</p> </blockquote> <p>Here’s a line for us to start with.</p> <p>This line is separated from the one above by two newlines, so it will be a <em>separate paragraph</em>.</p> <p>This line is also a separate paragraph, but… This line is only separated by a single newline, so it’s a separate line in the <em>same paragraph</em>.</p>]]></content><author><name>Albert Einstein</name></author><category term="distill"/><category term="formatting"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a distill-style blog post and main elements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with github metadata</title><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2020/github-metadata/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with github metadata"/><published>2020-09-28T21:01:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-28T21:01:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2020/github-metadata</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2020/github-metadata/"><![CDATA[<p>A sample blog page that demonstrates the accessing of github meta data.</p> <h2 id="what-does-github-metadata-do">What does Github-MetaData do?</h2> <ul> <li>Propagates the site.github namespace with repository metadata</li> <li>Setting site variables : <ul> <li>site.title</li> <li>site.description</li> <li>site.url</li> <li>site.baseurl</li> </ul> </li> <li>Accessing the metadata - duh.</li> <li>Generating edittable links.</li> </ul> <h2 id="additional-reading">Additional Reading</h2> <ul> <li>If you’re recieving incorrect/missing data, you may need to perform a Github API<a href="https://github.com/jekyll/github-metadata/blob/master/docs/authentication.md"> authentication</a>.</li> <li>Go through this <a href="https://jekyll.github.io/github-metadata/">README</a> for more details on the topic.</li> <li><a href="https://github.com/jekyll/github-metadata/blob/master/docs/site.github.md">This page</a> highlights all the feilds you can access with github-metadata. <br/></li> </ul> <h2 id="example-metadata">Example MetaData</h2> <ul> <li>Host Name :</li> <li>URL :</li> <li>BaseURL :</li> <li>Archived :</li> <li>Contributors :</li> </ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="external-services"/><category term="metadata"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[a quick run down on accessing github metadata.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with twitter</title><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2020/twitter/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with twitter"/><published>2020-09-28T15:12:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-28T15:12:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2020/twitter</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2020/twitter/"><![CDATA[<p>A sample blog page that demonstrates the inclusion of Tweets/Timelines/etc.</p> <h1 id="tweet">Tweet</h1> <p>An example of displaying a tweet:</p> <div class="jekyll-twitter-plugin"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="sv" dir="ltr">jekyll-twitter-plugin (1.0.0): A Liquid tag plugin for Jekyll that renders Tweets from Twitter API <a href="http://t.co/m4EIQPM9h4">http://t.co/m4EIQPM9h4</a></p>&mdash; RubyGems (@rubygems) <a href="https://twitter.com/rubygems/status/518821243320287232?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 5, 2014</a></blockquote> <script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script> </div> <h1 id="timeline">Timeline</h1> <p>An example of pulling from a timeline:</p> <div class="jekyll-twitter-plugin"><a class="twitter-timeline" data-width="500" data-tweet-limit="3" href="https://twitter.com/jekyllrb?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">Tweets by jekyllrb</a> <script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script> </div> <h1 id="additional-details">Additional Details</h1> <p>For more details on using the plugin visit: <a href="https://github.com/rob-murray/jekyll-twitter-plugin">jekyll-twitter-plugin</a></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="external-services"/><category term="formatting"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a blog post with twitter]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a post with disqus comments</title><link href="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2015/disqus-comments/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a post with disqus comments"/><published>2015-10-20T15:59:00+00:00</published><updated>2015-10-20T15:59:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2015/disqus-comments</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mysticbravo.github.io/blog/2015/disqus-comments/"><![CDATA[<p>This post shows how to add DISQUS comments.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="external-services"/><category term="comments"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[an example of a blog post with disqus comments]]></summary></entry></feed>